Register of the Opti-Mrs. Club of Madison Records, 1954-1996
Wisconsin Historical Society
Opti-Mrs. Club of Madison Records, 1954-1996
Opti-Mrs. Club of Madison (Wisconsin)
M2002-127
2.0 c.f. (1 archives box and 3 flat boxes)
Wisconsin Historical Society, Library-Archives Division
Records of the Opti-Mrs. Club of Madison, a womens social and civic organization affiliated with the Madison Optimist Club, organized in 1954 and disbanded in 1996; including minute books, by-laws, yearbooks listing members, scrapbooks, and other items documenting the activities of the group and its members.
Contents List
- History scrapbooks, M2002-127
  - 1954-1958 (Box 1, Volume 1)
  - 1958-1964 (Box 1, Volume 2)
  - 1964-1968 (Box 2, Volume 1)
  - 1968-1974 (Box 2, Volume 2)
  - 1974-1996 (Box 3, Volume 1)
- Constitution and by-laws, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Meeting minute books, 1954 April-1986 February (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
- Yearbooks, 1954/1955-1995/1995 (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
- Event announcements, 1965, 1979, 1988-1996 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Newsletters, 1963-1970, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- 9th District convention, Madison, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Favorite Recipes booklet, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)